{
  "a1": "Excellent considering he has to battle a coup d' etat from the democrats and the never trumpers as well as be President.",
  "a10": "Our trade policies are unfair to the USA.",
  "a11": "No. We gave Iran a time table in which could build nuclear weapons and gave him the funds in which to do it. They 're threatening Israel and our allies in that area .",
  "a12": "The one thing we should do is don't what Obama and his predecessors did. They paid bribes to North Korea to behave. Negotiate and if that doesn't work blow his test rockets out of the sky. Trump is handling it correctly.",
  "a2": "I support it. The economy is booming. Companies are bringing lots of their money back to the USA. This is creating millions of jobs. Blacks and Latinos are experiencing their lowest unemployment numbers ever.",
  "a3": "No . Trump's on the right track. Lower  taxes increases revenue and reduces debt.",
  "a4": "There is no economic inequality. People have to get themselves educated and trained for a 21 century world.",
  "a5": "We don't need any more laws. We need more God. A God fearing man don't go around shooting innocent people. America also need to vigorously enforce the  laws already on the books,",
  "a6": "USA should scrapped it. It was sold to us based on a pack of lies. You can't fix a lie.Buying across state lines will lower prices by increasing competition.",
  "a7": "As long as Baltimore is a sanctuary city no held from feds.",
  "a8": "They should enforce the laws already on the books. We crack down on states that legalize  recreational marijuana. It's a gateway drug to opioids and crack cocaine. All of my siblings that became  crack addicts started with marijuana.",
  "a9": "We should enforce the laws on the books.",
  "age": 66,
  "background": "retired owner financial services business",
  "directory": "content/us-house/district-3",
  "district": 3,
  "dob": "12/12/1951",
  "education": "undergraduate Delaware state university graduate coppin state university johns hopkin university",
  "filename": "thomas-e-pinkston-harris.md",
  "full-name": "Thomas E. \"Pinkston\" Harris",
  "jurisdiction": "Baltimore City",
  "last-name": "Harris",
  "party": "Republican",
  "q1": "How do you assess the Trump administration so far?",
  "q10": "Should the United States continue with the free trade policies it pursued for the last several decades, or should it enact restrictions in an attempt to help domestic industries?",
  "q11": "Do you support the Iran nuclear deal?",
  "q12": "How should the United States address the rise of North Korea’s nuclear program?",
  "q2": "Do you support or oppose the federal tax cuts passed in 2017? What effect do you believe they will have on the economy?",
  "q3": "Is the level of national debt a concern? What, if anything, should be done to reduce it or constrain its increase?",
  "q4": "Is the level of economic inequality in the United States a problem, and if so, what should the federal government do to address it?",
  "q5": "Should federal gun laws be changed, and if so, how?",
  "q6": "What should Congress do with respect to the Affordable Care Act? Should it be strengthened, and if so, how? Should it be scrapped? If so, what if anything should replace it?",
  "q7": "What role should the federal government play in helping cities like Baltimore?",
  "q8": "What can Congress do to address the opioid epidemic?",
  "q9": "What changes if any should Congress make to our immigration and deportation laws and policies?",
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "How do you assess the Trump administration so far?",
      "answer": "Excellent considering he has to battle a coup d' etat from the democrats and the never trumpers as well as be President.",
      "shortname": "Trump record"
    },
    {
      "question": "Do you support or oppose the federal tax cuts passed in 2017? What effect do you believe they will have on the economy?",
      "answer": "I support it. The economy is booming. Companies are bringing lots of their money back to the USA. This is creating millions of jobs. Blacks and Latinos are experiencing their lowest unemployment numbers ever.",
      "shortname": "2017 Tax cuts"
    },
    {
      "question": "Is the level of national debt a concern? What, if anything, should be done to reduce it or constrain its increase?",
      "answer": "No . Trump's on the right track. Lower  taxes increases revenue and reduces debt.",
      "shortname": "National debt"
    },
    {
      "question": "Is the level of economic inequality in the United States a problem, and if so, what should the federal government do to address it?",
      "answer": "There is no economic inequality. People have to get themselves educated and trained for a 21 century world.",
      "shortname": "Income inequality"
    },
    {
      "question": "Should federal gun laws be changed, and if so, how?",
      "answer": "We don't need any more laws. We need more God. A God fearing man don't go around shooting innocent people. America also need to vigorously enforce the  laws already on the books,",
      "shortname": "Gun laws"
    },
    {
      "question": "What should Congress do with respect to the Affordable Care Act? Should it be strengthened, and if so, how? Should it be scrapped? If so, what if anything should replace it?",
      "answer": "USA should scrapped it. It was sold to us based on a pack of lies. You can't fix a lie.Buying across state lines will lower prices by increasing competition.",
      "shortname": "ACA"
    },
    {
      "question": "What role should the federal government play in helping cities like Baltimore?",
      "answer": "As long as Baltimore is a sanctuary city no held from feds.",
      "shortname": "Urban policy"
    },
    {
      "question": "What can Congress do to address the opioid epidemic?",
      "answer": "They should enforce the laws already on the books. We crack down on states that legalize  recreational marijuana. It's a gateway drug to opioids and crack cocaine. All of my siblings that became  crack addicts started with marijuana.",
      "shortname": "Opioids"
    },
    {
      "question": "What changes if any should Congress make to our immigration and deportation laws and policies?",
      "answer": "We should enforce the laws on the books.",
      "shortname": "Immigration"
    },
    {
      "question": "Should the United States continue with the free trade policies it pursued for the last several decades, or should it enact restrictions in an attempt to help domestic industries?",
      "answer": "Our trade policies are unfair to the USA.",
      "shortname": "Free trade"
    },
    {
      "question": "Do you support the Iran nuclear deal?",
      "answer": "No. We gave Iran a time table in which could build nuclear weapons and gave him the funds in which to do it. They 're threatening Israel and our allies in that area .",
      "shortname": "Iran"
    },
    {
      "question": "How should the United States address the rise of North Korea’s nuclear program?",
      "answer": "The one thing we should do is don't what Obama and his predecessors did. They paid bribes to North Korea to behave. Negotiate and if that doesn't work blow his test rockets out of the sky. Trump is handling it correctly.",
      "shortname": "North Korea"
    }
  ],
  "race": "us-house",
  "residence": "Baltimore",
  "sn1": "Trump record",
  "sn10": "Free trade",
  "sn11": "Iran",
  "sn12": "North Korea",
  "sn2": "2017 Tax cuts",
  "sn3": "National debt",
  "sn4": "Income inequality",
  "sn5": "Gun laws",
  "sn6": "ACA",
  "sn7": "Urban policy",
  "sn8": "Opioids",
  "sn9": "Immigration",
  "survey-response": "LATE SUB",
  "title": "Thomas E. \"Pinkston\" Harris"
}
